{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651132930","data":{"timestamp":" 947651132930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651141279","data":{"timestamp":" 947651141279"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651155047","data":{"timestamp":" 947651155047"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651164395","data":{"timestamp":" 947651164395"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651170580","data":{"timestamp":" 947651170580"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 13"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651177781","data":{"timestamp":" 947651177781"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":"  "," userResponse":" ."," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" HES_1"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651178348","data":{"timestamp":" 947651178348"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 14"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" <space>"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651183931","data":{"timestamp":" 947651183930"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 12"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" <space>"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 1"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651185296","data":{"timestamp":" 947651185296"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651193744","data":{"timestamp":" 947651193744"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 73881cca-2a4b-4359-9f54-1fb28ace38fa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" word_copy"," tutorId":" write.sen.corr.ltr.stim_story_2.punc.2.1"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_Meno Aina Gani "," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651204825","data":{"timestamp":" 947651204825"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 5390968a-4ebd-4fd1-a2b0-056121fde0aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 9"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.addsub:0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651205816","data":{"timestamp":" 947651205816"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 5390968a-4ebd-4fd1-a2b0-056121fde0aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"write.sen.corr.ltr.stim:story_2.punc.2.2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651219699","data":{"timestamp":" 947651219699"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 5390968a-4ebd-4fd1-a2b0-056121fde0aa"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.addsub_0..8.incr.ADD-1-V.1"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_9_8-9-5"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651230046","data":{"timestamp":" 947651230046"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 87f784d0-d452-478b-8727-038dd1178ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MBUGA"," userResponse":" MBUGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651230269","data":{"timestamp":" 947651230269"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 87f784d0-d452-478b-8727-038dd1178ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651231234","data":{"timestamp":" 947651231234"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 87f784d0-d452-478b-8727-038dd1178ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WANYAMA"," userResponse":" WANYAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651232507","data":{"timestamp":" 947651232507"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 87f784d0-d452-478b-8727-038dd1178ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mbuga za wanyama Tanzania"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TANZANIA"," userResponse":" TANZANIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651235367","data":{"timestamp":" 947651235367"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 87f784d0-d452-478b-8727-038dd1178ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651236211","data":{"timestamp":" 947651236211"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 87f784d0-d452-478b-8727-038dd1178ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651236382","data":{"timestamp":" 947651236381"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 87f784d0-d452-478b-8727-038dd1178ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" songs"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947651236472","data":{"timestamp":" 947651236472"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000112_072514"," gameId":" 87f784d0-d452-478b-8727-038dd1178ac4"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__Safari_Song__it_32"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ya kwanza ni Serengeti"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANZA"," userResponse":" KWANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}